♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 7=
Governor,
he was right there in the cabinet.
Why did you...
On the wedding day, the moment we get
the phoenix crown, Xu You'an is dead.
In that case, we might as well
squeeze his last bit of value.
By sending Rong Xiaonan to his side
to help find the Buddha Head for me,
he'd die meaningfully.
What if Rong Xiaonan refuses?
With the ruse, he won't say no.
Mr. Rong,
from now on,
we're all in the same leaky boat.
If we want revenge,
we must first stay alive.
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
If you wish to find the Buddha Head,
take me to find the fake Jade Buddha Head,
and we'll get the clues.
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪The music halts, the song falls still♪
♪Wine cups go around amid laughter♪
(The voice of the man on stage
was exactly the same as my master's.)
(My master hasn't been
on stage for years.)
(And who was that woman?)
(She wore the kingfisher phoenix crown.)
(That is the opera world's
long-lost treasure.)
Hey.
The kingfisher phoenix crown.
My master and a dan actress in that crown
were singing "The Palace of Eternal Life".
I asked you to find the Buddha Head,
not some phoenix crown.
How dare you fool me?
Touch it.
If you don't get clues of Buddha Head,
you will go back to prison to rot.
A treasure of the opera world
and a treasure of Fengcheng.
The kingfisher phoenix crown
is connected to the Jade Buddha Head.
(Can someone truly sense
a thing's hidden truth through touch?)
If they are truly connected,
I'll find the kingfisher phoenix crown.
If the Buddha Head cannot be found
by then, you're done for.
Who is it?
Food is ready.
Enjoy your meal, gentlemen.
Sir,
here are your banknotes
and your train tickets.
Take them.
(Collect one hundred with this banknote)
The biggest figure
in Fengcheng is really generous,
offering a 100 gold bounty
on Xu You'an's life.
I really want to kill him now
and take the reward.
What's the rush?
There's a condition attached.
We can't make the move
until after his wedding.
Do you all understand?
Let me go!
Come here!
Who sent you?
As expected,
my foster father cares for me so much.
Don't kill me! Don't kill me!
Murder!
(Zhuzi, Young Rong Xiaonan)
Shitou.
(Shitou, Young Xu You'an)
What was your original name?
I didn't have a name.
I only got a name
after my master adopted me.
Then how long have you been
in the Rongqing Troupe?
I've been adopted by my master
since I was a baby.
Young Marshal, there's no need
to pry into my story.
Better use your time
to find the phoenix crown.
Let me go!
Miss Jiang?
Something's wrong.
Haha!
Let me go!
Let go!
I just heard from them
that Fengcheng's biggest figure
plans to kill you after your wedding.
I'm telling you,
we are the Xiao...
Mr. Rong, don't you know
she's my fiancee?
Why are you wearing this again?
Running from the wedding again?
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪